pharmaca.com 2017-09-28

# Privacy Policy | Pharmaca

## Your privacy is very important to us at Pharmaca.

We recognize your right to confidentiality and are committed to respecting your privacy and recognizing your need for appropriate protection and management of personal information you share with us (the phrase "personal information" means any information by which you can be identified, such as your name, mailing address, email address, telephone number, etc.). The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you what personal information we may collect from you, how we use such information, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to review and correct, the information.

## Types of Information Gathered

There may be times (such as when you purchase or order a product, or participate in contests, sweepstakes or promotions, etc.) when we ask you to provide certain information about yourself, such as your name, shipping/billing address, telephone number, email address, credit card information, birth date, gender, occupation, personal interests, etc. We may also maintain a record of your product purchases.

Whether or not to provide such information is completely your own choice. But if you choose not to provide the information we request, you may be unable to purchase products, or access certain services, offers and content on our web site. In addition, we may need to contact you via phone, email or mail to address questions or issues specific to your order, entry, etc., even if you have opted to not receive communications from us.

In general, you can visit many of our web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We may track the Internet domain address from which people visit us and analyze this data for trends and statistics, but individual users will remain anonymous, unless you voluntarily tell us who you are.

## Using Information About You

Pharmaca uses a secure third party, Cybersource, which is owned by Visa, to process customer payments safely and to detect fraud. When you complete an order with us, you are automatically opting in to allow your information to be submitted to Cybersource for processing. If you do not want your data to be transferred to a third party for payment processing, you should NOT complete an order with Pharmaca.

We use the personal information you provide for internal purposes, such as confirming and tracking your order, subscription or registration, analyzing trends and statistics, informing you of our new products, services and offers, and providing you with information from and about Pharmaca.

To serve you better, we may combine information you give us online or in our stores. We may also combine that information with publicly available information. We use that combined information to enhance and personalize your shopping experience with us, to communicate with you about our products and events that may be of interest to you, and for other promotional purposes.

Any personal information Pharmaca gathers from coupons (such as name, address and information about your purchases) delivered on our website or via email or direct mail will be never be sold. Pharmaca will only share the information with a very limited number of carefully selected partners who are contractually bound to only use the information for the above-mentioned purpose and exclusively with and for Pharmaca. Pharmaca must be in compliance with Federal HIPAA regulations. Therefore, personal data regarding individual customers' prescription medications will never be viewed, analyzed or shared.

To provide additional value to our customers, we may allow our vendors to provide offers to a select group of customers that may be interested in their brand(s). To ensure your personal data is protected, Pharmaca will obtain the materials from the supplier and communicate offers directly to our customers. In all instances, the information will only be used to provide information and offers regarding products and services available at Pharmaca.

Although unlikely, in certain instances we may disclose your personal information when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities who may be causing injury to you, to Pharmaca or to others. We may also disclose your personal information when we believe the law requires it.

## Information Sharing

Pharmaca will not sell or otherwise share personally identifying information with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide services to you at your request, or as required by law.

  Pharmaca may share aggregate data collected through its website that does not personally identify any party with other business partners in order to provide requested services that we do not provide directly. In these situations, this information will provided only in the aggregate and only to those information to other parties and agree not to use this information to solicit.

## Editing, Updating, Correcting and Deleting Information About You

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive information from Pharmaca Integrative please let us know by sending us an e-mail. Please be sure to include your e-mail address, mailing address, full name, and specifically what information you do not want to receive. If you would like to update or correct your email address, mailing address or other personal information with us please contact us the same way.

Please note that any requests to remove or update your personal information may take up to ten days per e-mail-removal request, and 6-8 weeks per postal mail-removal request.

## Protecting Children

Pharmaca takes special care to protect the safety and privacy of children. Our websites are general audience sites. We do not permit anyone under the age of 13 to register with us. We also do not send e-mail correspondence to anyone who tells us that they are under the age of 13 without their parent's consent.

Parents should always supervise their children while online. Pharmaca’s website is not designed nor intended to collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen. So that we may comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, we ask that children under the age of thirteen not provide any personal information on this website.

## Cookies

Our websites use "cookies". A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Generally, we use cookies to remind us of who you are, tailor our products and services to suit your personal interests, estimate our audience size, track your status in our promotions, contests and sweepstakes, and/or analyze your visiting patterns. You may occasionally get cookies from our business partners (e.g., advertisers, tracking utilities, and partner programs on our Site, such as the Google Trusted Stores and Google Analytics Advertisers Programs) or other third parties with links on our Site.You can generally set your browser to not accept cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. Pharmaca will only use this type data in an aggregate form which does not identify you personally.

## Security

We take precautions, including use of sophisticated encryption and authentication tools, to protect the security of your personal information that you share with us. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our websites, and you do so at your own risk.

We urge you to keep your password in a safe place and not to divulge it to anyone. Also remember to log off your account and close your browser window when you have finished your visit. This is to ensure that others cannot access your account, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place such as a library or Internet cafe.

## Links to Third Party Sites

Our websites may contain links to websites operated and maintained by third parties, over which we have no control. Privacy policies on such linked sites may be different from our privacy policy. You access such linked sites at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a linked site before disclosing any personal information on such site.

## Policy Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy in whole or in part, we will inform you by posting a notice on our website. Those changes will go into effect on the date posted in the notice. The new policy will apply to all current and past users of our website and will replace any prior policies that are inconsistent.

**(Last Updated August, 2010)**
